{
    "subject": "resource/Robert_Edouard_Moritz",
    "predicate": "property/placeOfDeath",
    "object": "Seattle, Washington",
    "human_readable": "Robert Edouard Moritz died in Seattle, Washington.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9562000036239624,
            "question": "Is there any historical significance to Robert Edouard Moritz's death in Seattle?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9476497769355774,
            "question": "Was Robert Edouard Moritz from Seattle?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.911263108253479,
            "question": "Where did Robert Edouard Moritz die?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8565515875816345,
            "question": "What is the name of the state where Robert Edouard Moritz died?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8523114919662476,
            "question": "Was Robert Edouard Moritz a notable figure in Seattle?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.832209050655365,
            "question": "What year did Robert Edouard Moritz die?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6702902913093567,
            "question": "In which city in Washington state did Robert Edouard Moritz pass away?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5625311732292175,
            "question": "What was Robert Edouard Moritz known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.45299628376960754,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about Robert Edouard Moritz's life?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3864284157752991,
            "question": "Do you know anything else about Robert Edouard Moritz?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Robert Edouard Moritz died in Seattle, Washington.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2588_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me more about Robert Edouard Moritz's life?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2588_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What was Robert Edouard Moritz known for?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2588_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In which city in Washington state did Robert Edouard Moritz pass away?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2588_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2588_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2588_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2588_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2588_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2588_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2588_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2588_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2588_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2588_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2588_75.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information provided in the documents supports that Robert Edouard Moritz died in Seattle, Washington. Specifically, one of the text snippets states: \"He died in Seattle in the state of Washington in 1940 at the age of 72.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {'output': 'yes'}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}